The wind?
Are you awake?
I hailed us a Pegasus Carriage.
Huh?
Flying so high must've
been cold in your pajamas.
We're almost there.
There, can you see it?
That's my atelier and
the school you'll be learning at.
I planted Guard Briar seeds
around your house.
They'll grow in no time
and act as a barrier.
Your house was petrified
by an unknown spell,
so it'll keep people
from getting too close to it.
So...
Coco?
What's the matter?
I promised my mom I wouldn't
leave her by herself.
But I...
Coco...
Don't be hard on yourself.
You didn't know what you were doing.
Here, let's wash your face.
Let all your tears out, then look ahead.
Because this is going to
be your new home starting today.
Um, what is this?
Hmm? Water, of course.
Ah. I totally forgot!
You need a change of clothes.
It feels too round and floaty
to be called water.
Huh?
How am I supposed to use this?
Mister Qifrey?
I'm scared of touching
magic I don't understand.
There's nothing to be afraid of!
It's not a difficult
kind of magic to handle.
Want me to teach you?
That's a Vapor Bubble.
It's magic that pulls water
out of the moisture in the air.
Here, hold out your hands.
Tilt the lower tray,
and the water pours out.
Wow, that's amazing. Thank you.
Thank you!
Huh?
I love being told "Thank you."
So thank you!
Oh, um... I see.
Thanks.
Thank you for thanking me again!
Thank you for thanking me,
and thank you again...
Just ignore her if she's too much.
She'll stop eventually if you
just don't respond.
How mean, Richeh! I was just helping her.
The pen and ink.
Are you both witches?
Just apprentices.
We're students of Master Qifrey.
Wait, so you're not?
I totally thought you were
a fellow student like us.
Are we the same age?
Which atelier did you come from?
Uh...
I don't think I can call myself
a student just yet.
I mean, yesterday was
the first time I ever drew a spell.
But I'm going to live here as of today.
What?
Huh?
Wait, so you're the one who did it?
Did what?
There's a rumor going around
about an Outsider who used
forbidden magic...
That they were allowed to become an
apprentice with their memories intact...
Coco.
Are you okay?
Mr. Qifrey...
Looks like you all introduced yourselves.
Richeh and Tetia,
will you go study in your rooms
after helping with the morning chores?
Okay!
Here are your new clothes.
This is what my students wear.
Don't be afraid. I'll explain everything.
Looks like it fits you perfectly.
Now then, let us begin
the story of magic.
Long ago, magic wasn't something special.
All you needed was a combination of
known patterns and specially made ink.
It was a familiar tool
that anyone could use.
However, it sparked conflict
time and time again.
When humans are given
the power to do anything,
"anything" is what they will do.
And so, many horrific spells were created.
The few people who still had a conscience
turned away from conflict
and unified as witches
to take other people's memories of magic,
entrusting the secret only to
disciples sworn to protect it.
That was the Day of the Pact.
Ever since then,
people have been made to believe
that magic is a power only
a chosen few can wield.
If the truth were to spread,
the world would collapse
into lawlessness once again.
Everyone's being careful
to keep the secret.
That's why they started
talking about you.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
No, I brought this on myself.
Um, what's "forbidden magic"?
Magic that was drawn
during the age of conflict
and banned when the Day of the Pact came—
magic for hurting others.
Please teach me!
Teach me all about the magic
that I'm not supposed to use!
I want to know!
I'll be too scared to do anything
if I don't know what it is.
This is where I usually tell
my students not to rush things,
but that's harder with you.
Come with me.
There are countless forbidden spells,
but it's simple when you boil it down.
Any spell cast directly upon
the human body
is prohibited under all circumstances.
This includes transformation,
age alteration,
teleportation without
doors or conveyances,
as well as the manipulation
of thoughts or emotion,
the harming of others,
or even healing them.
There is, however, a single exception.
Erasing memories?
Exactly.
Most spells are cast on tools.
Like carriages or lamps.
Or windows like this one.
A lake?!
But we were surrounded
by hills just a minute ago.
It's called a Windowway.
It connects two round windows
that bear the same pattern.
Can you see that building over there?
That's the Tower of Tomes.
To preserve knowledge,
all books related to magic
are duplicated there
the moment they're written.
The picture book...
Let's go there right now!
I won't sleep until I find it!
Hold your horses.
That was the Librarians' Trial.
The Tower of Tomes
is protected by four librarians,
and only witches who overcome it
are allowed to enter.
So you need to study
if you want to go inside.
Coco.
It made me happy earlier when you
expressed how eager you are to learn.
It's natural to feel fear.
But...
The spells that are not forbidden
are those that bring
happiness to all of us.
So why not learn about
the gentler sort of spell?
That's how I feel.
What do you say?
Yes. Of course, Master Qifrey.
This'll be your room.
Looks like Agott's not around.
Who's Agott?
Your roommate.
The two of you will share a workspace.
You'll have your own bedroom, though.
Go down the stairs in the back.
Don't worry, the doors can be locked.
You should get some rest.
I have some things to take care of,
so call if you need anything.
It's me, Qifrey.
Thank you for allowing me
to take in Coco as my apprentice.
Yes. No, nothing about the picture book.
She's overwhelmed right now.
So this is what a witch's room looks like?
That's my side of the desk.
Move so I can land.
Oh, sorry.
You're Agott, right? I'm Coco—
I know who you are.
You're the Outsider
everyone's talking about.
I heard you'll be joining as a new peer.
I'm sorry about your mother.
Th-Thanks.
Because of what you've done,
she'll never return to being human.
I came here to save her.
By becoming a witch—
Our whole lives, we've been
drawing Casting Seals
until our fingertips turned black.
We worked and worked
until we passed the tests,
and were only then allowed to
become apprentices.
You're an ordinary girl who knows nothing.
There's no way an Outsider such as
yourself can become a witch.
I... I've drawn spells already!
I won't know until I try it!
Then prove yourself.
Your tests start tomorrow—
Agott! Coco!
Food is ready!
Let's eat!
I'm starving.
Me, too! We're having
Coco's welcome party today!
Lots of food.
Same as usual.
Master, what happened
to the welcome party?
It was so last-minute.
We'll do it another time.
Where's Agott?
She said she's eating in her room.
She should join us once in a while.
Okay, let's eat.
Would you do the honors, Coco?
Huh? Uh, sure.
Let's eat.
It's so good.
I know, right? We bake it ourselves.
Master is a great chef.
That's amazing.
It's thanks to the locally grown wheat.
We get great veggies around here.
Thank you for the food.
Mom...
I need to take tests in order
to become an apprentice.
But it doesn't go into detail
about what you need to do.
Need to do about what?
There are lots of things books
don't tell you when it comes to magic.
You'll learn more
from doing than from reading.
What are these?
Your Components—
tools used to draw magic.
Wow!
They look so cool!
The Ink Wand. A pen.
I still feel a bit scared
touching this. But...
Mom, I'm going to save you
no matter what it takes!
Master Qifrey, I look
forward to our lessons.
Okay, let's get started.
Are you okay, Coco?
Shall we take a break?
I-I'm fine.
Okay, try explaining to me
what you learned.
O-Okay.
Um... A spell is composed
of three elements.
The sigil is in the center.
It's surrounded by lines
that are called signs.
The outer circle that
completes it is called the ring.
The types of sigil—fire,
water,
light,
and wind.
They determine what kind
of magic it becomes.
The signs determine
what form the magic takes,
as well as its size and direction.
Lastly, when the outer ring is completed,
that locks the seal in place
and activates the spell.
I'm barely keeping up
just memorizing everything.
But you were able to explain it!
I'm going to try drawing one!
I like it! That's the spirit.
Huh?
Don't throw it away.
No! Please don't look at it!
It's not something I can show you!
It's sloppy, and the lines
are all wobbly and messy...
Of course it is. You're just learning.
But there's something else you
should pay attention to.
Look right here.
See how your ring is not connected?
A spell won't activate
unless it's a complete circle.
It's natural to have unsteady hands when
you're learning to use a new tool.
You're like a newborn
foal just learning to stand.
You'll get used to it and be
running around freely in no time.
Now, connect the lines
and activate the spell.
I-I'm sorry! Very sorry!
It was an accident!
Sorry! I'll dry it! I'll dry it off!
Calm down, Coco!
Has it dried?!
Sorry, Agott. Are you okay?
Not yet?!
It's fine, Master.
I'm not bothered by it at all.
But may I see the Casting Seal she drew?
Huh? Sure.
Ah, I found the problem.
Look.
This sign is longer than the rest.
It amplified pressure in this direction
and caused the water to gush out.
As always, your observation
is on point, Agott.
I think I can leave her in your care.
Huh?
For the next two or three days,
I'll be out visiting the Great Hall.
Please look after her
while I'm gone, Agott.
Absolutely, Master.
Wait!
There's a lot you can learn
from your peers.
Watch her closely and learn, Coco.
M-Master...
Um, I'm really sorry about that. I—
You don't have to keep apologizing.
I said I wasn't bothered by it, didn't I?
Now then, Coco.
Yesterday, I told you to prove yourself.
No more cushy little lessons.
Your tests start now.
What?