There are many kinds of magic,
but four are considered
particularly important.
Granting control to that nourishing
force, the source of all life—
the Sigil of Water.
Turning stone to sand and sand to stone,
enabling transformation and
movement—the Sigil of Earth.
That which frees us
to visit distant realms,
and has fueled so much progress—
the Sigil of Levitation.
And that which has become
humanity's sword and shield—
the Sigil of Flame.
Witches refer to these
as the Primary Tetrad.
So, let's give them a try.
Wh-What do I do?!
A-Are you all right?
Thank you, Tetia...
Thank you for thanking me!
What were you doing, anyway?
I was drawing the Pyreball spell as
part of my levitation magic practice.
The Sigil of Fire deals with formless
phenomena, so it can be dangerous
if it's not maintained at just
the right size and balance.
Be careful when you're using it.
I will.
I thought you'd mastered
levitation magic at the Dadah Range.
Why do you need to practice it now?
You were out there
zoom-zoom-zooming around!
Zoomie-zoomie-zoom!
I ruined the Sylph Shoes
Agott lent me at the time.
I wanted to fix them up
before returning them.
I've finished everything except
the Casting Seal on the soles,
but my lines keep coming out wobbly...
Maybe this isn't the right pen for you?
Different people need
different weights and grips.
This is just one of my old ones.
Maybe we should have you
pick one out for yourself?
Coco, let's go to the magic stationer's!
Magic stationer's?
Yes. They stock all kinds
of magical goods.
It's an art supply store.
An art supply store?
Let's go to the magic stationer's.
M-Magic stationer's?!
It's like a dream!
Coco? Hello?
It's still sinking in.
Just give me a moment.
That's Kalhn, Township of the Marshwoods.
It's that island on the sandbar,
and it's the closest witches'
town to where we live.
Wait for me!
So, the Casting Seal to
make your skirt fuller...
My wand's finally taking
the ink properly, so...
So many witches...
To protect the city from the molewyrms
in the Marshwoods on the far bank,
the witches built part of the sandbar
into an island to support a watchtower.
Witches started to gather here,
it grew into an atelier town,
and they haven't even
built a bridge to it...
Master Qifrey, Coco's not listening!
Excuse me.
I have better things to do
than play tour guide for Coco.
I'm going off on my own.
There are shops I want to visit.
We'll meet up at the magic stationer's!
How are things going with Agott?
Well...
I really wish we could be closer.
Hey!
We're over here!
It's like a dream!
Coco!
We're not supposed to get separated!
Kalhn's just full of people, isn't it?
I'm tired.
This is the magic stationer's,
the Starry Sword.
There's a tree growing through
the middle of the shop...
Well, well.
I don't often see a witch's apprentice
wonderstruck by a Silverwood Tree.
You really don't know
something so elementary?
Don't be like that.
Coco hasn't been an apprentice for long.
Then this is the famous...
Well, that does explain it!
Do forgive me, dearie.
I didn't recognize you either, so...
I guess that makes us even!
This is Mister Nolnoa!
He's the owner of the magic
stationer's, the Starry Sword!
Indeed.
All the Components here were made
by me and my grandson Tartah.
All the pens,
all the ink...
Every last one!
I can also extract Conjuring Ink
at whatever concentration you want.
Extract...?
Coco, was it?
I'll show you. Come along, now.
Yes, sir!
It turned black!
That's Woodcruor.
The branches are a silvery white
when they're healthy,
but turn black when they die.
It's toxic in that state,
both to the tree and to humans.
But once we dissolve it in water,
then strain out the excess...
We've got ourselves crude Conjuring Ink,
the source of all magic.
Regular ink is made from the soot that's
produced when you burn normal wood,
but Conjuring Ink is different.
It's made from the cruor—
the literal "blood"—of the tree.
So Silverwoods are extremely
important trees to witches.
Yes indeed!
For some reason, it's the only tree
from which we can extract the ink.
It sounds like an amazing tree!
A precious tree.
That's right! There's an
old legend about it, too!
Yes, the legend says that long ago,
a Silverwood tree fell
in love with a witch!
It offered its blood to be ink,
and its branches to be wands...
Wands?
So, did you come here to buy a wand?
Yes!
Well, then...
Go test a few out.
Use this to do it.
I'm sure you'll find the perfect wand.
What should we go for?
I like lighter wands myself!
I wonder which I should try...
W-Wait!
Coco?
Wh-What do we do?
Don't know.
But she'll get lost if we
leave her on her own.
We have to find her!
What?!
Agott!
What's going on?
Come with us!
H-Hang on!
What's this all about?
Coco! Come back!
Wait up, Coco!
What are you doing, Coco?
Where do you think you're going?
I... I saw that person!
The one who gave me
the forbidden magic book!
That witch...
What?
What a ridiculous wild goose chase.
But at least we stayed together!
C'mon, let's go back to the shop!
Hey.
The scenery's too different here
for us to just be one alley down.
The brushbuddy's gone, too.
You may be right.
It looks completely different.
The walls and floors are made of
a white stone you don't see in Kalhn.
Which means...
this isn't Kalhn.
Th-That can't be true!
We didn't pass through a Windowway,
and it's not like we could just teleport!
I'll just have a look from above!
Tetia may be on the right track.
We could have been directly
teleported without realizing it.
But spells like that
aren't allowed, right?
That would be...
Forbidden magic.
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
This is totally not Kalhn!
We gotta get out of here!
Wait a minute!
Tetia, what's wrong?
Tetia, calm down!
What exactly did you see?
It's less what I saw
and more what saw me!
I have no business with the others, but...
Coco, welcome to the world of magic.
You are our hope.
Mr. Nolnoa, have you seen my apprentices?
Oh?
I assumed they got bored
and went for a walk.
How could they get bored?!
This is the best store in the whole town!
I could spend all day browsing in here!
Shucks, I'm blushing!
They're also not the sort of girls
who'd run off without thanking you.
Where could they be?
I saw them.
They ran after a strangely dressed witch.
The witch had a mask that
looked like an eyeball...
Stay as you are.
Maintain eye contact
and back up very slowly.
Once we're far enough,
I'll give the word,
then we'll run with all our might.
Steady...
Now!
Now's our chance! Run!
Agott, that spell was amazing!
Was it a fire spell?!
It used the Sigil of Fire surrounded
by the Sign of Spiraling Wind.
And you drew it that fast?!
Of course not!
You draw the spells in advance
in your Palm Quire,
then you can use them in a second
just by closing the ring!
You're amazing, Agott! So cool!
Do you even realize the danger we're in?!
Agott!
Awful news! We hit a dead end!
Do we take another path?
Wh-What do we do?
The dragon's going to
track us down and eat us...
I don't want to die.
I haven't left a single
spell to the world!
Why did this have to—
Tetia, get a grip.
We're witch apprentices.
We'll find a way out with our magic.
I'll use a Wall Breaker spell
to create an escape hatch.
Richeh, Tetia, buy us time.
Right.
Understood.
There.
Where should I draw it?
Around here, maybe...
Add the signs to this sigil...
Hey, Agott. Check this out!
I think a Casting Seal like this
should buy us enough time.
I saw it in her eyes.
She blames me for this.
Yes, that should do it.
But... she's right to.
Please...
Fly!
That should buy us a little time.
Well done, Tetia.
Nice.
Tetia's amazing.
Is that...
Hey, Agott!
I'm sorry! I...
What is wrong with you?!
You don't touch someone
while they're drawing!
I'm sorry! I didn't do it on purpose!
Didn't do it on purpose?!
Yes, I'm sure you didn't!
Turning your mother into stone,
putting us in danger...
You didn't mean to do
any of it, did you?!
But it's all still your fault, Coco!
Get it through your head
how ignorant you are,
and just stop doing anything!
Wh-What do we do?
I don't have time to start over.
We'll have to go back and find another—
I've got it.
Amazing. Great work, Richeh.
Let's put this dead end behind us.
I meant this part of the maze...
though you can take it
either way you want to.
Tetia.
Master Qifrey, what should I do?
Qifrey!
Any sign of the girls?
No, they're not anywhere
outside, at least.
I didn't expect...
that the Brimmed Caps would
make contact themselves.
Wait!
That was one of the Brimmed Caps?
I wouldn't have dreamed
one would come here!
A dangerous faction that
wears hats from a bygone era
and hides their faces behind masks.
I thought Coco would afford us a clue,
but I didn't expect them to come to her.
Tartah, do you remember anything else?
Anything at all?
Um, I'm really sorry.
I don't remember much.
I see.
Wait, you're...
You're the brushbuddy
that Coco brought back.
Were you with them?
Do you know where they went?
It'll be getting dark soon.
Please, everyone...
Be safe!