kaze no tsute ga hakondekureru
The winds whisper of my next chapter
tsuki ni odoreba yoru ni somaru madou
Nights glistening anew with sorcery
kawaku hodo ni mitasarenai
I can barely stand to let the ink dry
kono shunkan ga hoshikute
I've been waiting for this all along
mada wakaranai mayoeru kohitsuji no you
So much to learn that I hardly know where to begin
nanimono demo nai tokubetsu de wa nai you de
But even though I don't think I'm all that special
asu ga hoshikatta tadorubeki sekai no yoake e to
I won't stray from the path that leads to my dreams
koe ga hibiku kimi to kimi no
My voice and yours in unison
itsuka wo tsunagu unmei no you na
As if fate meant to bring us together
kasanariau kyoumei no anthem
An anthem built from our harmony
wazuka na inori idaku hibi yo
Every note a prayer held dear
dare yori egaita kibou omou yume mo
All I've hoped and longed for so much
inochi no iro ga kagayaku mahou
Giving life color is its own magic
sono chikara ga nakutatte mou
Even if I am ever without this power
mayou koto wa nai sa
Each step will take me that much closer
fushigi na hibi yo
Every day a new wonder